(Penny:)I knew I could smell 'em.
(Adam:)What about
from when you were a kid?
(Sheldon:)Oh, certainly.
Uh, when I was eight years old,
(Sheldon:)Billy Sparks cornered me
in the playground.
(Sheldon:)I asked myself,
“What would Spock do?”
(Sheldon:)Then I grabbed Billy
on his shoulder
(Sheldon:)and performed
my first Vulcan nerve pinch.
(Adam:)Did it work?
(Sheldon:)Oh, no... he broke my collarbone.
(Sheldon:)I can still hear it click.
(Leonard:)That must have been
very upsetting for you.
(Sheldon:)Oh, not at all.
(Sheldon:)As I said, the entire point
of emulating Spock
(Sheldon:)was to rise above human emotion,
(Sheldon:)which I've spent
a lifetime mastering.
Oh... (sputters)
(Sheldon:)Excuse me?
(Raj:)I'm sorry.
I'm not here.
No. You went (sputters).
What does (sputters) mean?
(Sheldon:)Um...
You did go (sputters).
Okay, fine.
Well, Sheldon, I'm no expert,
(Penny:)but aren't you completely
missing the point of Spock?
(Penny:)I mean, he liked to act
(Penny:)like he had no emotions,
but he was still half human.